Hi!  I'm Richard Stallman, leader of the Free Software Movement
and founder of the GNU project
which developed the free software operating system GNU
Welcome to this course "The Road to the Free Digital Society"
In this course we will cover issues of human rights
that arise from computing. We will talk about threats to the Free Digital Society
Will explain what Free Software means
and what makes a program free and how you make your programs free
We will talk about copyright law
and copyleft which is based on it
We'll talk about how these freedom issues do or don't apply to other kinds of digital works
besides software
We will recognize some of the propaganda used  by the opponents of digital freedom
and how to avoid repeating it
And we will talk about some of the thin changes
we need to make (some of us) in our own lifestyles
so that we recover some of the digital freedom that many have lost
Happy hacking! And I hope this course will get you started on the path to freedom.